Guide to the DoubleTake Records, 1908-1999, bulk 1994-1999 RL.00321
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2010-0081): DoubleTake Records, 1993-1998, 281241; 41 boxes
  - Straw, Gerald, 281380 (Box 36)
  - Street, Richard, 281379 (Box 36)
  - Strong, Bruce, 281378 (Box 36)
  - Stummer, Helen M., 281377 (Box 36)
  - Sturdevant, Sandra, 281376 (Box 36)
  - Stylianon, Krystallena, 281375 (Box 36)
  - Suchy, Miso, 281374 (Box 36)
  - Sugerman, Debra, 281373 (Box 36)
  - Sultan, Larry, 281372 (Box 36)
  - Sundra, Michael, 281371 (Box 36)
  - de Swaan, Sylvia, 281370 (Box 36)
  - Swarts, Matt, 281369 (Box 36)
  - Sweeney, Marla, 281368 (Box 36)
  - Swinson, Lee, 281367 (Box 36)
  - Swift, Thor, 281366 (Box 36)
  - Szabo, Joseph, 281365 (Box 36)
  - Szarkowski, John (2 folders), 281364 (Box 36)
  - Tarver, Ron, 281363 (Box 36)
  - Tehrani, Alex, 281362 (Box 36)
  - Tellgren, Anna, 281361 (Box 36)
  - Temple, Charlotte, 281360 (Box 36)
  - Tenneson, Joyce, 281359 (Box 36)
  - Thall, Bob, 281358 (Box 36)
  - Thibaut, Emiliano, 281357 (Box 36)
  - Thode, Scott, 281356 (Box 36)
  - Thomas, Chip, 281355 (Box 36)
  - Thomas, Katrina, 281354 (Box 36)
  - Thompson, Jerry, 281353 (Box 37)
  - Thurber, Shellburne, 281352 (Box 37)
  - Tice, George (2 folders), 281351 (Box 37)
  - Tirana, Amina, 281350 (Box 37)
  - Tobin, Mark, 281349 (Box 37)
  - Toensing, Amy, 281348 (Box 37)
  - Tolan, William, 281347 (Box 37)
  - Tonningsen, Peter, 281346 (Box 37)
  - Toplikar, Susan, 281345 (Box 37)
  - Torres, Aurelio, 281344 (Box 37)
  - Touchet, Leo, 281343 (Box 37)
  - Towell, Larry (3 folders), 281342 (Box 37)
  - Tourlentes, Stephen, 281341 (Box 37)
  - Traikos, Lori, 281340 (Box 38)
  - Traister, Michael, 281339 (Box 38)
  - Traube, Alex, 281338 (Box 38)
  - Tress, Arthur, 281337 (Box 38)
  - Troeller, Linda, 281336 (Box 38)
  - Tucker, Toba, 281335 (Box 38)
  - Tulis, Thomas, 281334 (Box 38)
  - Turczan, Katherine, 281333 (Box 38)
  - Turk, Elizabeth, 281332 (Box 38)
  - Turner, Michael, 281331 (Box 38)
  - Turok, Antonio, 281330 (Box 38)
  - Tynan, Jim, 281329 (Box 38)
  - Urrea, Lewis, 281328 (Box 38)
  - Uhlenbeck, Erica, 281327 (Box 38)
  - Vachon, John, 281326 (Box 38)
  - Vassiliov, Andreas, 281325 (Box 38)
  - Vaughn, Caroline, 281324 (Box 38)
  - Vernant, Pierre, 281323 (Box 38)
  - Venezia, Anthony, 281322 (Box 38)
  - Vera, Jorge, 281321 (Box 38)
  - Verburg, JoAnn, 281320 (Box 38)
  - Verene, Chris, 281319 (Box 38)
  - Vergara, Camilo Jose, 281318 (Box 38)
  - Vigtel, Gudman, 281317 (Box 38)
  - Vitali, Massimo, 281316 (Box 38)
  - Vizzini, Nancianne, 281315 (Box 38)
  - Vizzini, Robert, 281314 (Box 38)
  - Wade, Harry, 281313 (Box 38)
  - Wagner, Catherine, 281312 (Box 38)
  - Waldman, Max, 281311 (Box 38)
  - Walker, Shawn, 281310 (Box 39)
  - Wallace, Scott, 281309 (Box 39)
  - Wallis, Dawna (2 folders), 281308 (Box 39)
  - Walsh, James, 281307 (Box 39)
  - Walsh, Wendy, 281306 (Box 39)
  - Walters, Joanne, 281305 (Box 39)
  - Wang, Harvey, 281304 (Box 39)
  - Ward, Frank, 281303 (Box 39)
  - Warner, William, 281302 (Box 39)
  - Waters, Tom, 281301 (Box 39)
  - Watters, Diana, 281300 (Box 39)
  - Webb, Alex, 281299 (Box 39)
  - Weems, Carrie Mae, 281298 (Box 39)
  - Wegman, W., 281297 (Box 39)
  - Weider, Alan, 281296 (Box 39)
  - Weider, Mary, 281295 (Box 39)
  - Weil, Brian, 281294 (Box 39)
  - Weisbrot, Michael, 281293 (Box 39)
  - Weiss, Hans, 281292 (Box 39)
  - Weitz, Jessica, 281291 (Box 39)
  - Wells, David, 281290 (Box 39)
  - Welty, Eudora, 281289 (Box 39)
  - Wemple, C.T., 281288 (Box 39)
  - West, Bruce and Sharon, 281287 (Box 39)
  - West, Judy, 281286 (Box 39)
  - West, William K., 281285 (Box 39)
  - Wharton, David, 281284 (Box 39)
  - Whitehouse, Deborah, 281283 (Box 39)
  - Wichs, Steve, 281282 (Box 39)
  - Widmer, Christian, 281281 (Box 39)
  - Willard, Tom, 281280 (Box 39)
  - Williams, Graeme, 281279 (Box 39)
  - Williams, Jeannette, 281278 (Box 39)
  - Williams, Sye, 281277 (Box 39)
  - Williamson, Michael, 281276 (Box 39)
  - Willis, Deborah, 281275 (Box 39)
  - Willis, John, 281274 (Box 39)
  - Wilner, Augusta, 281273 (Box 39)
  - Wilson, Harry, 281272 (Box 39)
  - Wilson, Lee, 281271 (Box 39)
  - Winogrand, Garry, 281270 (Box 39)
  - Winogrand, Garry, 281269 (Box 40)
  - Winokur, Michael, 281268 (Box 40)
  - Wise, Marc, 281267 (Box 40)
  - Withers, Ernest C., 281266 (Box 40)
  - Wohlheter, Walter P., 281265 (Box 40)
  - Wolf, Linda, 281264 (Box 40)
  - Wolin, Jeffrey, 281263 (Box 40)
  - Wolke, Joy, 281262 (Box 40)
  - Wolvovitz, Ethel, 281261 (Box 40)
  - Wood, Jasper, 281260 (Box 40)
  - Wood, Tom, 281259 (Box 40)
  - Woodman, Donald, 281258 (Box 40)
  - Winningham, Geoff, 281257 (Box 40)
  - Worswick, Clark, 281256 (Box 40)
  - Wrbican, Sue, 281255 (Box 40)
  - Wright, Corina, 281254 (Box 40)
  - Wright, Holly, 281253 (Box 40)
  - Wright, Willie Anne, 281252 (Box 41)
  - Wynn, Jessica, 281251 (Box 41)
  - Wynroth, Via, 281250 (Box 41)
  - Yalom, Ben and Reid, 281249 (Box 41)
  - Young, Barbara, 281248 (Box 41)
  - Young, D.C., 281247 (Box 41)
  - Younker, Richard, 281246 (Box 41)
  - Zeibell, Robert, 281245 (Box 41)
  - Zeiger, David, 281244 (Box 41)
  - Zelman, Bil, 281243 (Box 41)
  - Zimbel, George, 281242 (Box 41)